{
    "subject": "resource/Whitworth_University",
    "predicate": "ontology/campus",
    "object": "resource/Suburb",
    "human_readable": "The campus of Whitworth University is in a suburb.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9835845232009888,
            "question": "Is Whitworth University in a city or suburb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9610157012939453,
            "question": "Is Whitworth University a rural or suburban university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9499118328094482,
            "question": "Where is the campus of Whitworth University located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8756855726242065,
            "question": "In what type of area does Whitworth University reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8662995100021362,
            "question": "Where is the Whitworth University campus situated relative to a city center?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8405929803848267,
            "question": "How would you characterize the location of Whitworth University's campus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8230044841766357,
            "question": "What type of area is home to Whitworth University's campus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7968499064445496,
            "question": "Is the Whitworth University campus in a densely populated or less populated area?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.795164167881012,
            "question": "Would you describe Whitworth University as being in an urban or rural setting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5669759511947632,
            "question": "What kind of environment surrounds the Whitworth University campus?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The campus of Whitworth University is in a suburb.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5488_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would you describe Whitworth University as being in an urban or rural setting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5488_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the Whitworth University campus in a densely populated or less populated area?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5488_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of area is home to Whitworth University's campus?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5488_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5488_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5488_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5488_154.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5488_159.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5488_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5488_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5488_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5488_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5488_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5488_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Whitworth University is located in the suburb of Spokane, Washington. Therefore, the triple \"The campus of Whitworth University is in a suburb\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}